<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Communication on Brett Randall Taylor</title>
    <link>https://www.hitfuturenow.com/tags/communication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Communication on Brett Randall Taylor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hitfuturenow.com/tags/communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Historical Work in Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://www.hitfuturenow.com/blog/2020/11/25/2020-11-25-historical-work-in-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hitfuturenow.com/blog/2020/11/25/2020-11-25-historical-work-in-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>  Historical Locations     Time Period City State Company Job Type Description    1979-1990 Sacramento California Sutter General Hospital O/R Attendant Multiple work including Software Support for MUMPs Sugical Scheduling system. Ran data related Performance improvement for the O/R.  1989 - 1990 Sacramento California Sutter General Hospital Patient Care Operating Analyst Data Analysis of Nursing  1990-1991 Sacramento California Sutter Health Information Systems Programmer Analyst Data development - Perinatal Management System / Accounting Data  1991-1993 Sacramento California Sutter Health Information Systems Strategic Planning Analyst Capitation for capitated market, Healthcare Information System     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Verbal Communication In Leadership</title>
      <link>https://www.hitfuturenow.com/blog/2019/04/03/2019-04-03-non-verbal-communication-in-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hitfuturenow.com/blog/2019/04/03/2019-04-03-non-verbal-communication-in-leadership/</guid>
      <description>As a leader, you need to understand that your facial expressions are important.
 Leaders sometimes are not focused on how they are sharing their expressions with others when speaking with staff members. Please take a look why this all matters, and how you realize that non-verbal communication often provides a receiver with information that many not make them happy.
Take a look at how I respond in the video!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>